



BISH MORGAN

I've always been interested in stories. And finding a brand's story, telling it on the right platform, can make a real impact in people's lives. Over four years, I have contributed strategies to one of the UK's largest advertisers and helped save 11 lives from drowning. With versatile experience at independent agencies and one of the largest strategy departments in London, I am motivated to make culturally relevant and highly effective work.

Education

University of Oxford

BA Hons English Language & Literature

Grade 2:1

Quotes

"A highly productive selfstarter," – Malcolm White, Planning Founder, krow

"Bish is an excellent planner. He is smart, open and brings out the best in others. Whether that's creatives, other planners or the client. I'd always be happy to hear I'm working with Bish on a project." – Helen Spencer, Planning Director, Strat House

Experience

Strategist | Wunderman Thompson | 2021—present (1 year, 1 month)

Awarded Brief of the Month for the best brief in the agency. Led strategy across many projects or else worked alongside the Strategy Partner. Clients: Microsoft, BT, KPMG, Costa Coffee.

- Campaign Strategy: Created a targeted digital strategy to gain and nurture leads for Microsoft's industry clouds, consulting across paid and owned media. Ran creative workshops for ideation briefs on Microsoft and BT. Defined strategy for KPMG's first ever global campaign.
- Research: Led qualitative interviews across a variety of projects.
 Guided and briefed the data department to prepare social listening and web scraping reports.

Planner | krow | 2018—2021 (2 years, 9 months)

Promoted from Planning Executive to Planner in a year. Guided day-to-day strategy and provided support to Strategy Director. Clients: DFS, Wilko, RNLI.

- Campaign Strategy: Developed insights and campaign strategies for quarterly DFS campaigns, including the <u>Grand Comfort Sale</u> featuring Wallace & Gromit.
- Brand Strategy: Defined brand strategies and created guidelines for DFS master brand and sub-brands including Grand Designs and Halo.
- Research: Conducted focus groups for the Holland & Barrett pitch and designed multiple quantitative surveys.

Planning Intern | CP+B, VCCP, Founded | 2016—2017 (4 months)

Gained experience at several respected London agencies with a valuable sense of how different strategy departments operate.